Jun paid me money so I you know I love
money that people pay me money I'll do
whatever they want
what about NASCAR CNN no who wanted
coding tutorial sorry I was in the
middle of a very heated game of League
of Legends that I did end up losing
tragically but it was close and we could
have won
now I'm kind of tired guys all right I
do all you all a coding tutorial but
what I can't do is come up with the idea
like I was going to teach you how to
count the alphabet PHP you can do it
slower if you want learning so there's a
problem where this doesn't count to two
that and that's because when we echo you
know dollar sign Z plus plus that
doesn't work because you can't you have
to assign a variable to that but if I
echo dollar sign a feed that Z but if I
actually do a plus one especially a a so
when you add letter and PHP I don't know
why I lag am i lagging lagging you guys
are lagging I'm watching my stream right
there
she Street was like I all right guys I'm
going to sleep
I promised you coding I feel bad I feel
terrible but it's so late no you know
what I'm excited though I'm gonna brush
my teeth
let's go get a toothbrush and I'll brush
my teeth oh it's Jane
that sounds good
alright guys we got the toothpaste and
the toothbrush
we're gonna put toothpaste on the
toothbrush steer very carefully in view
of the webcam I really like this
toothbrush because it has a timer for
each quadrant of my mouth you guys will
see so I turn it on I asked the lower
right corner my mouth
I live alone there's just a lot of
people around here usually there's
actually one of you intern clothes here
I know you listen see how mighty so I
should stop a little bit that's the
signal to switch quadrants
what do you want me a code in PHP
hey Rick when there's two fucking stream
oh wow you gotta tell me what the code
not found hard
my hands touch down because of how well
how can anything
again after the Gaussian Oh
he's watching his done
okay right again to match the Gaussian
distribution I'm not really sure how to
do that what do you mean by that
okay so we have our beautiful Gaussian
distribution I'm not sure what you mean
by I don't know mighty MUX it's all
public if you go my github geo geo
textile slash configuration
you
that work
did that come back how do you develop
this personality I don't know you guys I
knocked with a watt and the phone into
the wire on my computer okay so I'm not
sure what you mean by again that can
output that Gaussian distribution let me
think about what that means all right so
when again you have a generator and a
distributor at a discriminator so each
point you want to know whether it came
from the real distribution with a fake
distribution hmm I mean this is a cute
toy exercise to think about right
I mean the problem not tensorflow
like this isn't really gonna work
because don't leave one dimensional
right
I think ganz only work in like really
high dimensional space that's right so
if you think about the manifold of like
an image right where you think about
each pixel is a dimension the manifold
is extremely like weird looking and what
again is doing is making it look we can
play with that kind of stuff let's think
about it like well so the other downside
is I don't really have a GPU in this
computer maybe one day we can stream I
have I bought an external GPU thinking I
could do machine learning with it but
it's very hard to get tensorflow GPU on
the Mac
[Music]
so this is a thing
okay.we training a neural network to
sample from the simple 1d normal
distribution let DNG be small three
layer perceptrons each with a meager the
discriminator takes out
okay okay this is doable okay we'll
think about this a bit no no there's
more fun I like this I like this problem
don't go to sleep okay
uniform zero one okay so the goal is to
transform beautiful um zero one
normal
[Applause]
should be able to use CPU tensorflow
no I don't think I can pick install
tatse for GPU I don't think what's gonna
work this'll work
wait to my mother break again
okay
[Music]
no this is stupid
it's just using why does this keep
alright assume every night pretty much
get to Nathanael we got focus all right
so let's not look at too much of this
code I'll be streaming tomorrow night
probably playing Morley legends such a
way that the mappoint clustered densely
where P data X's dense G takes in Z
yards fake data X so that's an easy net
to think about should we use cross for
us makes life easy
new tutorial here off the top of my head
[Music]
input is 1 they said they had 11 in here
that's telling them and then obviously
my activation can't be softmax with me
output so well let's first the first
thing that we should try to do before we
do Gavin since we can cheat on this and
we can actually always just get a look
up it's big Gaussian I think we want the
probability distribution yeah the
cumulative distribution function how do
you do this how do you sample from a
gaussian normally i don't know any RFS
like this is not an obvious thing to do
especially since like once you get to
the long tails of sequential what you
get to the long tails of the gaussian
right okay so there
the probability density formation how do
you sample let's just look at sampling
from a Gaussian me like old school way
to do it
Wow yeah the inverse distribution
function but like there isn't a normal
way to do this
no you won't
Oh JSTOR fuck JSTOR sure these authors
are great put J's toys evil guys can
look good love to find out why Susanoo
between zero and one PDF what value of x
will P of X equal P be the equation no
yeah okay that's a negative two ratings
so that's wrong
Wow I don't know anything about coming
yeah come on related they just use my
name one of these days I'll sue them
like okay so you can see what the
functions are right
[Music]
hmm
meanwhile the discriminator takes an
input X and outputs a likelihood of the
import belonging to P data
well you're already telling me that I
need a way to sample for my distribution
so that's a scam all right like you see
what I'm saying like I would need a
sample from my Gaussian distribution in
the first place I mean I guess I could
do that with numpy
she's a code for this does that work
so I want the inverse cumulative
distribution function
Oh
this is hard
now let's not look at that stuff because
it's cheap okay so if you want a sample
from the model and then I assure you it
goes well you can just stick in believe
that random is Python is the step is a
normal sample right switches have to
play along at home okay when we're
actually best target distributions all
this I was copying the definitions I
don't read their code sample of a noise
distribution X
so I sample right now my mom is a real
tap them okay so now when we pass in
this random distribution in maps to this
our target distribution is they have a
name for this shit
so you got rhythm like I'm tired okay
so that's the real distribution now we
need a discriminator so call this one D
she got four decks they said eleven way
side eleven to their god we actually
like freeze the weights of some of these
don't we
listen till when I use Adam it's too
complicated
inappropriate serial walrus
inappropriate this is a PG rated channel
we have family-friendly
one day I want Kellogg's cereal to
advertise on my twitch channel and if I
ever want Kellogg's we have to behave in
a family friendly manner Kellogg's
cereal but you buy frosted flakes
totally the tiger and Michael Phelps
smoking a ball ask can't say my thoughts
about goodbye that's not family-friendly
yo knew everything about them that's
crazy so what do we want to do we don't
care about the discriminator predicting
correctly
what is the gam trick again okay I don't
want to read that cuz we're trying to do
it from scratch that's thing yeah if I
think about this a little bit that it's
fine okay we want the generator when we
go through of the generator and the
discriminator
[Music]
- pol has know how to do tendon right
nose easier
cow lodge you guys Kellogg's one day
Kellogg's will sponsor my twitch channel
and then I'll finally make money off of
twitch fuck them fuck that me I can't
say I don't know what the what that
means
I have family-friendly channel guys
family-friendly o x equals MV dot or ax
oh I got emails I don't know what any of
that stuff means
alright let's say H oh cool change
alright good all right let's
discriminate a lot we love
discriminating don't tell anybody
alright good train so good
[Music]
- sighs will default to 32 that party
will attempt a 410 at box
oh good oh look train so good
oh look at that okay all right um let's
just train for - okay so that trains the
disco thats right this is a Christian
Channel
I know that one I so we train the
discriminator now train generator this
is a lot harder I think I just have to
say something why D D equals sequential
GD is like that eg that compile all of
this is gonna work
don't be sad freeze the weights this is
what gets annoying like I want to back
prop through the discriminator but I
want to freeze the weights you know I'm
saying Christian channel YX point okay
um all these weights leave the light on
the freezer layer layer dark trainable
let's do it the lair level and endured
the mod xi d dot trainable not like
apply it to all the lair that'd be so
nice oh so much okay I'll say that
fanboy equals so change generator okay
what do we want to train here basically
on my fake samples well that's probably
a little stupid too because it should be
non stationary distribution dumb anyway
I think we just want to generate random
data we're gonna use the random store
before actually I don't want to say Gd
that's right
let's compile the model wait whatever my
mom like elite that I'm such a noob Oh
actually no nevermind I'm going on a
date tomorrow
no screaming sorry wow you all show up
for this stuff flow attribute has no
shape of course floats have no shape
just like try to shape a float it's like
alright ya gotta make that Z capital
brah
alright is the loss going down oh oh
yeah look at that loss
[Applause]
we can put the weights
[Music]
[Applause]
Oh
[Music]
[Applause]
so histogram right guys never gonna
always been again
[Music]
wait so that was to go through
it's totally different
[Music]
[Applause]
all right this family guys you should
forgive me it's late you don't forgive
me
well Wow look at all these people y'all
showed up can't leave now we got a
streaming audience oh this isn't a other
song yet another good one anytime this
one
[Music]
1990-1999
and makes the sellout that ring is sell
out I know a sellout when I see one oh
boy
[Applause]
[Music]
yeah
alright that was perfect timing I think
we're good now if anyone wants to play
along at home I'll throw this on a guest
I'll throw this on the paceman or
something yeah that's too hard never
mind I take it back I lied bro it's liar
again I know you alright so that's what
it starts looking like the goal is to
make the orange look like the blue oh
that's better well it learned the mean
can learn the variance
alright guys I think that might be what
you get tonight
be warned joying alright so let's see
after it learns for one thingy okay now
it went over there again is garbage now
I'll use I'll use better than
Oh
all right it's getting stuck in this
like shuffle XY to be right no try a
couple app box we've done trainable
equals false
I mean maybe we want different randoms
Shh
no we do want different randoms yeah no
we doing different atoms
that's adapter
I'm tired that's something
Oh
mmm
and he's Adam I should all be predicted
to be one even though they're fake
because that's what fights against
[Music]
yeah
my only concern is that generator
trainable thing is still changing the
way to the generator see now look I try
to trim the discriminator and I can't
learn anymore this is a great problem to
understand dance thank you - whatever
your name was trumpet Jean your bro this
is a good problem I'm gonna layer in
there dude deep learning
so the goal if this thing works is that
the orange should line up with the blow
okay so look slightly unbalanced these
things are apparently incredibly painful
to tune
let's turn the learning right down right
and yeah MSE is all fine
there's only zeros and ones and gas man
which is fine
Wow someone changed PLT has two vets
those tops piss me off bins integer
sequence
not work oh yeah
that's actually exactly a lot more like
what I would expect as possible our plot
was just broken
it was crappy what's not learning that
was learning
my only concern I guess is that it's
changing the way to the discriminator
[Music]
I'm having this problem before with
cross games it just doesn't listen wait
there's no way to like get that high so
I can actually put the weights no
[Music]
function
actually this is bullshit
[Music]
this cracker said d dot that wave will
say once you have the weights the
discriminator are changing
okay that's good that's a lot of weights
we shouldn't change
my job
okay that works cans are just really
unstable
well yeah it's just more
oh look I'm going to converging Oh
exciting now it went past converging oh
no its continuing to go oh great okay
right faster
that's background one
okay looks like gams are unstable
garbage maybe some wrong
don't worry about you hi
let's go
all right cans are in stable garbage I'm
gonna sleep I'll pass this to you guys
without poops a closed twitch guess
without github
see they removed anonymous Slough sorry
I lost the chat hey spit what's hast
been this any good he's elegant paste
new can I Drive file here no ghost bit
private there red tree ipfs bet code pad
if there's any good pipe
so more tech cement oh my god these are
the lowest quality things I've ever seen
let's try a spit again what did I have
fun with hey spend save
I've got CoffeeScript got it wrong huh
cute though I can just access it as
anything very sensible okay if anybody
would like to play along at home there's
the link enjoy
I will twitch tip anybody who makes it
work to post your haste bin tomorrow it
kind of worked for me and will read the
thing thank you for joining
that was twitch programming it's 2:00 in
the morning I'm gonna sleep glad people